<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata><NPS_Info><MetaPurp>OnlineData</MetaPurp><MetaPurp>CSDGM</MetaPurp><MetaPurp>NPS</MetaPurp><NPS_Unit><UnitCode>MOJA </UnitCode><UnitType>Park</UnitType></NPS_Unit><DatStore><Category>Boundary </Category><Category>Land Status / Ownership </Category><DataSite>NR-GIS</DataSite><DSteward><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>NPS - Land Resources Division, WASO-FC </cntorg><cntper>Roger Johnson </cntper></cntorgp><cntpos>Chief Cartographer </cntpos><cntaddr><addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype><address>301 South Howes Street Suite 208 </address><city>Fort Collins </city><state>CO </state><postal>80522 </postal><country>USA</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>970-484-6428 </cntvoice><cntfax>970-484-6432 </cntfax><cntemail>PPFL_LandsNet@nps.gov  </cntemail><hours>7:00am-5:30pm Mountain Monday-Thursday </hours></cntinfo></DSteward></DatStore></NPS_Info><idinfo><citation><citeinfo><origin>Department of the Interior (DOI), National Park Service (NPS), Land Resources Division (LRD), Pacific West Land Resources Program Center </origin><pubdate>20220915  </pubdate><title Sync="FALSE">Mojave National Preserve Tract and Boundary Data </title><edition>20220915  </edition><pubinfo><pubplace>San Francisco, CA </pubplace><publish>National Park Service Land Resources Division </publish></pubinfo><onlink>http://nrdata.nps.gov/programs/Lands/moja_tracts.zip </onlink><geoform>vector digital data</geoform></citeinfo></citation><descript><abstract>These ESRI shape files are of National Park Service tract and boundary data that was created by the Land Resources Division. Tracts are numbered and created by the regional cartographic staff at the Land Resources Program Centers and are associated to the Land Status Maps. This data should be used to display properties that NPS owns and properties that NPS may have some type of interest such as scenic easements or right of ways. </abstract><purpose>This data is intended to keep a record of ownership information. Tracts can represent several types of interest like fee and scenic easement, and can be under several types of ownership like NPS owned, private, other federal, state or county. This data set provides accurate and reliable ownership data for park management and acquisition priorities.</purpose><langdata Sync="FALSE">en</langdata></descript><timeperd><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>19941031 </begdate><enddate>20220915  </enddate></rngdates></timeinfo><current>Beginning date is the first recorded conveyance date. Ending date is set to the last day the data set was updated. </current></timeperd><status><progress>Complete</progress><update>Continually </update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc>-116.164549</westbc><eastbc>-114.949471 </eastbc><northbc>35.591233 </northbc><southbc>34.716968 </southbc></bounding><lboundng><leftbc>2483040.622469</leftbc><rightbc>2518025.292190</rightbc><bottombc>287903.395080</bottombc><topbc>313117.765448</topbc></lboundng></spdom><keywords><theme><themekt>ISO 19115 Topic Category</themekt><themekey>Boundaries</themekey><themekey>Planning Cadastre </themekey></theme><theme><themekt>None</themekt><themekey>Boundary</themekey><themekey>Ownership</themekey><themekey>Parcels</themekey><themekey>Tracts</themekey><themekey>LRDCAB </themekey></theme><theme><themekt>National Park Service Theme Category Thesaurus</themekt></theme><place><placekt>None</placekt><placekey>United States </placekey><placekey>National Park Service </placekey><placekey>Mojave National Preserve </placekey><placekey>Pacific West </placekey><placekey>California </placekey></place><place><placekt>National Park System Unit Name Thesaurus</placekt></place><place><placekt>National Park System Unit Code Thesaurus</placekt></place></keywords><accconst>None </accconst><useconst>NPS Director's Order #25 states: "Land status maps will be prepared to identify the ownership of the lands within the authorized boundaries of the park unit. These maps, showing ownership and acreage, are the 'official record' of the acreage of Federal and non-federal lands within the park boundaries. While these maps are the official record of the lands and acreage within the unit's authorized boundaries, they are not of survey quality and not intended to be used for survey purposes." As such this data is intended for use as a tool for GIS analysis. It is in no way intended for engineering or legal purposes. The data accuracy is checked against best available sources which may be dated and vary by location. NPS assumes no liability for use of this data. The boundary polygons LRD creates represent the current legislated boundary of a given NPS unit. NPS does not necessarily have full fee ownership or hold another interest (easement, right of way, etc...) in all parcels contained within this boundary. Equivalently NPS may own or have an interest in parcels outside the legislated boundary of a given unit. In order to obtain complete information about current NPS interests both inside and outside the units legislated boundary, the tracts file created by LRD should be used in conjunction with this boundary file created by LRD.</useconst><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>NPS - Land Resources Division, WASO -Fort Collins, CO </cntorg><cntper>Chief Cartographer  </cntper></cntorgp><cntpos>Cartographer </cntpos><cntaddr><addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype><address>301 South Howes Street, Suite 208 </address><city>Fort Collins </city><state>CO </state><postal>80521 </postal><country>USA </country></cntaddr><cntvoice>970-484-6428 </cntvoice><cntfax>970-484-6432 </cntfax><cntemail>PPFL_LandsNet@nps.gov  </cntemail><hours>0700-17:30 MST M-F </hours></cntinfo></ptcontac><citeinfo>Microsoft Windows XP - Service Pack 2, Autodesk Land Desktop 2006 Project (DWG format)  </citeinfo><natvform Sync="FALSE">Shapefile</natvform></idinfo><dataqual><attracc><attraccr>The Tract_id, and Alpha data fields are provided by regional cartographic offices. The Date_Edit data field is added when the regional office submits the data to the Lands WASO Fort Collins office for inclusion in the national data set. All remaining tract attributes are updated from LRD's Master Deed Listing (MDL) nightly. By default the Status and Estate fields are included shape file dbf. All other MDL fields covered under the FOIA can be added to the tract dbf upon request.</attraccr></attracc><logic>Link and node polygon topology is created using Autodesk Civil3D 2015 project.. The data is then exported to ESRI shape file format and reprojected from it's native Autodesk coordinate system to NAD83 generic latitude and longitude, LL83. </logic><complete>Information contained in LRD's land ownership databases is updated nightly however tract polygons are posted to the NPS Data Store on a monthly basis. Users can ensure parcel polygons have up to date ownership attribution after the publication date by contacting your regional LRD office or downloading the Current_Tract_Ownership_Data file located on the NPS Data Store (http://science.nature.nps.gov/nrdata/) in a dBase format. Please contact the data originator with any suggested corrections and updates. LRD's boundary polygons represent the current legislated boundary of a given NPS unit. NPS does not necessarily have full fee ownership or hold another interest (easement, right of way, etc...) in all parcels contained within this boundary. Equivalently NPS may own or have an interest in parcels outside the legislated boundary of a given unit. In order to obtain complete information about current NPS interests both inside and outside the units legislated boundary, LRD's tracts files should also be downloaded and used in conjunction with LRD's boundary files. </complete><posacc><horizpa><horizpar>It is estimated that this data sets meets National Map Accuracy Standards for 1:100,000 scale data. That is, 90 percent of all points tested are within 1/50th of an inch (167 feet). </horizpar></horizpa><vertacc><vertaccr>None</vertaccr></vertacc></posacc><lineage><srcinfo><srccite><citeinfo><origin>National Park Service - Land Resources Division </origin><pubdate>20220915  </pubdate><title>Legal Descriptions </title><edition>N/A </edition><geoform>document - legal description </geoform><pubinfo><pubplace>Pacific West Land Resources Program Center </pubplace><publish>Land Resources Division </publish></pubinfo><othercit>NA </othercit></citeinfo></srccite><srcscale>1 </srcscale><typesrc>Paper </typesrc><srctime><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>19941031 </begdate><enddate>20220915  </enddate></rngdates></timeinfo><srccurr>Beginning Date represents first conveyed date. Ending date is when the data was last updated. </srccurr></srctime><srccitea>Legal Descriptions </srccitea><srccontr>tract and boundary geometry, Tract_id, Alpha </srccontr></srcinfo><srcinfo><srccite><citeinfo><origin>National Park Service - Land Resources Division </origin><pubdate>20220915  </pubdate><title>Deeds </title><edition>N/A </edition><geoform>document - deed </geoform><pubinfo><pubplace>Pacific West Land Resources Program Center </pubplace><publish>Land Resources Division </publish></pubinfo><othercit>NA </othercit></citeinfo></srccite><srcscale>1 </srcscale><typesrc>Paper </typesrc><srctime><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>19941031 </begdate><enddate>20220915  </enddate></rngdates></timeinfo><srccurr>Beginning Date represents first conveyed date. Ending date is when the data was last updated. </srccurr></srctime><srccitea>deeds </srccitea><srccontr>tract and boundary geometry, Tract_id, Alpha </srccontr></srcinfo><srcinfo><srccite><citeinfo><origin>National Park Service - Land Resources Division </origin><pubdate>20220915  </pubdate><title>Segment Maps </title><edition>N/A </edition><geoform>map - segment map </geoform><pubinfo><pubplace>Pacific West Land Resources Program Center </pubplace><publish>Land Resources Division </publish></pubinfo><othercit>NA </othercit></citeinfo></srccite><srcscale>1200 - 36000 </srcscale><typesrc>Digital </typesrc><srctime><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>19941031 </begdate><enddate>20220915  </enddate></rngdates></timeinfo><srccurr>Beginning Date represents first conveyed date. Ending date is when the data was last updated. </srccurr></srctime><srccitea>segment maps </srccitea><srccontr>tract and boundary geometry, Tract_id, Alpha </srccontr></srcinfo><procstep><procdesc>Minor revisions was done on 9/15/2020. No revision was made to the boundary. Tract 160-03 was divided into three tracts. The geometry Tracts 144-49 and 144-50 was adjusted (See C.O. # 114). The topology was updated on 9/18/2019, tract 144-14 was divided into three tracts and Tract 192-22 was divided into two tracts. PUBLIC LAW No. 116-90 (03/12/2019) Natural Resources Management Act boundary of preserve was adjusted to include 25.00 acres of of Bureau of Land Management land located in Baker, California. So the tract topology also was updated to included the new tract. Tract 114-35 made up three county parcels 0544-291-114 (10.00 ac.), 0544-291-16 (5.00 ac.) and portion of 0544-351-06 (5.00 ac.) All parcels are described as an aliquot parts in Sections 19 and 30 of T 14 N, R 9 E, San Bernardino Base &amp; Meridian. a Only the tract topology was updated due to the acquisitions of 96 tracts done in February of 2017. A minor discrepancy of an aliquot parts description was found by a BLM geographer, therefore boundary of preserve was modified. The discrepancy was located on the E-W south-south 1/64 centerline of Section 10, T 14 N, R 17 E, San Bernardine Base &amp; Meridian. The boundary was moved 660 feet easterly on said centerline from C-S-SE 1/64 corner of said section to SE-SE-1/64 corner of Section 10 to be consisted with legal description of the preserve. The layer of Tract 109-03 was revised from Tract to Tract-Sec. There were four individual tracts each tract was divided into two tracts. The boundary between Tracts 197-14 and 197-15 was revised. Boundary adjustment published in the Federal Register on June 14, 2013 [NPS-PWR-MOJA-12321; PS.SMOJA0003]. SUMMARY: Notice the boundary of Mojave National Preserve is modified to include 7.12 acres of improved land identified as Tract 103-28 and to exclude 48.14 acres of improved land identified as Tract 114-05. The entire line work of park boundary and the individual tracts were re-drawn based on the latest BLM CadNSDI PLSS Data a geodatebase for State of California (FGDB dated 09/19/2011). In process of re-mapping of the digitized centerlines of the Kingston Road and Nipton Road was done in ArcGIS. Cogo-ing hardcopies of right-of-way maps of Interstate 15 and Interstate 40. These right-of-way maps were provided by the Department of Transportation of the State of California (CALTRANS District 8). Park boundary of the park in NW portion is right-of-way of Interstate 15 and in southern portion is the right-of-way of Interstate 40. ROW linework in section 1 of T 15N R 11E, sections 5 and 6 T 15N R 12E, and sections 24, 25, 26, 27, 31, 32, and 33 of T 16N R 12E were rotated around the section corner common to sections 17, 18, 19, and 20 of T 16N R 12E 1 degree. ROW linework in section 22 T 15N R 14E, and sections 32, 33, and 34 T 16N R 14 E was rotated around the west quarter corner of section 22 T 15N R 14E 0d 40'. ROW linework in sections 1, 2, 11, 14, 15, 21, and 22 T 13N R 8E was rotated around the section corner common to sections 25, 26, 35, and 36 of T 14N R 8E 0d40'. ROW linework in section 36 T 14N R 8E and sections 20, 29, 30, and 31 T 14N R 9E were rotated around the section corner common to sections 16, 17, 20, and 21 T 14N R 9E 0d25'. ROW linework in sections 1, 10, 11, 15, 16, and 21 T 14N R 9E, section 6 T 14N R 10E, and sections 31 and 32 T 15N R 10E were rotated around the corner common to sections 16, 17, 20, and 21 T 14N R 9E 1d. ROW linework in sections 28 and 29 T 15N R 10E were rotated around the corner common to sections 28, 29, 32, and 33 T 15N R 10E 1d. ROW linework in sections 13, 22, 23, and 24 T 15N R 10E, and sections 8, 9, 10, 11, 17, and 18 in T15N R 11E were rotated around the corner common to sections 21, 22, 27, 28 T 15N R 10E 1d. Tracts 153-04, 153-05, 153-06, 153-07, 153-08, 153-09, 153-10, 153-11, 153-14, 153-15, 153-16, 153-17, 153-18 and portion of 143-03 were transformed X = 7267289.24, Y = 2199939.78 (NE corner of Sec.25) and 7261917.55, Y = 2194560.90 (SW corner of Sec. 25) to account for the ground to grid translation. All of these tracts located in Sec. 25, T. 11 N, R12 E., S.B. B. &amp; M. Two transformed points were derivated from GCDB Data. Tract 118-01A rotated around 1°23’46.54674” from Latitude 35°18” 55.765” N and Longitude 115°33’01.681”W (NAD 83). Tract 103-28 is outside the park boundary and it’s described in the California State Plane Coordinate System of 1983, Zone 5 same as cad file for Mojave NP. NAD83 California State Planes, Zone 5, US Foot was used as the source coordinate system for the Autodesk Civil3D 2012 project. The Autodesk line work is imported, edited, attributed, approved, and a link and node topology is developed both for the tract and boundary data layers according to the procedures described in the Land Acquisition Procedures Manual Chapter 5. The entire unit is created in a geographically contiguous model space and separate layouts representing each individual segment map are created. The tract and boundary data is then reprojected to North American Datum 1983 generic latitude &amp; longitude and exported from Autodesk to an ArcView shape file format in a single step. This data dates back to 2004. It was first made available in 2016.</procdesc><procdesc>Update 03212019: Tract and boundary topologies were updated to include 25.00 acres added to preserve per change order #112 Tract 114-35. The tract topology was updated to reflect the changes in change order 8386-11. It was discovered that the parcels had not been assigned separate NPS tract numbers, and that their acreage was mistakenly lumped in with tract 104-01. </procdesc><srcused>Deeds, Segment Maps, Legal Descriptions and Misc. Maps from the NPS LandsNet Archive (http://landsnet.nps.gov/tractsnet/documents/MOJA/) </srcused><procdate>20090827 - 20220915  </procdate><proccont><cntinfo><cntperp><cntper>Regional Cartographer  </cntper><cntorg>Pacific West Region Land Resources Program Center </cntorg></cntperp><cntpos>Cartographic Technician </cntpos><cntaddr><addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype><address>333 Bush Street, Suite 500 </address><city>San Francisco </city><state>CA </state><postal>94104-2828 </postal><country>USA</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>415-623-2123 </cntvoice><cntfax>415-623-2381 </cntfax><cntemail>PPFL_LandsNet@nps.gov </cntemail><hours>0800- 1700, M-F PST </hours></cntinfo></proccont></procstep></lineage></dataqual><spref><horizsys>
		- 

		- 

		- 

		- 

		- 

		- 

		- 

		- 
<geograph><latres>0.000002</latres><longres>0.000002</longres><geogunit>Decimal degrees</geogunit></geograph><geodetic><horizdn>North American Datum of 1983</horizdn><ellips>Geodetic Reference System 80</ellips><semiaxis>6378137.000000</semiaxis><denflat>298.257222</denflat></geodetic></horizsys></spref><eainfo><detailed><enttyp><enttypl Sync="FALSE">moja_tracts.dbf </enttypl><enttypd>Shapefile Attribute Table </enttypd><enttypds>None </enttypds><enttypt Sync="FALSE">Feature Class</enttypt><enttypc Sync="FALSE">226</enttypc></enttyp><attr><attrlabl Sync="FALSE">Alpha </attrlabl><attrdef Sync="FALSE">Provides the unit identification code. </attrdef><attrdefs Sync="FALSE">"Land Acquisition Procedures (LAPS)", revised 2017. </attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="FALSE">Attributes were created according to the National Park Service, Washington Land Resources Division, Land Acquisition Procedures (LAPS) revised 2005. </udom></attrdomv><attalias Sync="FALSE">Alpha </attalias><attrtype Sync="FALSE">String </attrtype><attwidth Sync="FALSE">4 </attwidth><atprecis Sync="FALSE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="FALSE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="FALSE">Tract_id </attrlabl><attalias Sync="FALSE">Tract_Id </attalias><attrtype Sync="FALSE">String </attrtype><attwidth Sync="FALSE">256 </attwidth><atprecis Sync="FALSE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="FALSE">0</attscale><attrdef Sync="FALSE">Provides the tract identification number. </attrdef><attrdefs Sync="FALSE">"Land Acquisition Procedures (LAPS)", revised 2017. </attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="FALSE">Attributes were created according to the National Park Service, Washington Land Resources Division, Land Acquisition Procedures (LAPS) revised 2009. </udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="FALSE">Status </attrlabl><attrdef Sync="FALSE">Defines if an interest is a parcel is NPS owned, held by another Federal agency or a non-Federal party. </attrdef><attrdefs Sync="FALSE">15"Land Acquisition Procedures (LAPS)", revised 2017. </attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="FALSE">Attributes were created according to the National Park Service, Washington Land Resources Division, Land Acquisition Procedures (LAPS) revised 2009. </udom></attrdomv><attalias Sync="FALSE">Status </attalias><attrtype Sync="FALSE">String </attrtype><attwidth Sync="FALSE">16 </attwidth><atprecis Sync="FALSE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="FALSE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="FALSE">Estate </attrlabl><attrdef Sync="FALSE">Expresses the degree, nature, quality, or extent of an interest NPS has acquired. </attrdef><attrdefs Sync="FALSE">"Land Acquisition Procedures (LAPS)", revised 2009. </attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="FALSE">Attributes were created according to the National Park Service, Washington Land Resources Division, Land Acquisition Procedures (LAPS) revised 2009. </udom></attrdomv><attalias Sync="FALSE">Estate </attalias><attrtype Sync="FALSE">String </attrtype><attwidth Sync="FALSE">16 </attwidth><atprecis Sync="FALSE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="FALSE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="FALSE">Areatract </attrlabl><attrdef Sync="FALSE">A field used to relate each parcel to the Current_Tract_Ownership_Data.dbf file located on the NPS Data Store. </attrdef><attrdefs Sync="FALSE">"Land Acquisition Procedures (LAPS)", revised 2017. </attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="FALSE">Attributes were created according to the National Park Service, Washington Land Resources Division, Land Acquisition Procedures (LAPS) revised 2009. </udom></attrdomv><attalias Sync="FALSE">Areatract </attalias><attrtype Sync="FALSE">String </attrtype><attwidth Sync="FALSE">16 </attwidth><atprecis Sync="FALSE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="FALSE">0</attscale></attr></detailed><overview><eaover>Attributes were created according to the National Park Service, Land Resources Division, Land Acquisition Procedures (LAPS).</eaover><eadetcit>"Land Acquisition Procedures (LAPS)", Mapping Standards - Chapter 5, revised 2009. </eadetcit></overview></eainfo><distinfo><distrib><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>NPS - Land Resources Division, WASO-FC </cntorg><cntper>Chief Cartographer </cntper></cntorgp><cntpos>Chief Cartographer </cntpos><cntaddr><addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype><address>301 South Howes Street Suite 208 </address><city>Fort Collins </city><state>CO </state><postal>80522 </postal><country>USA</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>970-484-6428 </cntvoice><cntfax>970-484-6432 </cntfax><cntemail>PPFL_LandsNet@nps.gov </cntemail><hours>7:00am-5:30pm Mountain Monday-Thursday </hours></cntinfo></distrib><distliab>Property ownership data is compiled from deeds, plats, surveys, and other source data. These are not engineering quality drawings and should be used for administrative purposes only. The National Park Service shall not be held liable for improper or incorrect use of the data described and/or contained herein. These data and related graphics are not legal documents and are not intended to be used as such. The information contained in these data is dynamic and may change over time. The data are not better than the original sources from which they were derived. It is the responsibility of the data user to use the data appropriately and consistent within the limitations of geospatial data in general and these data in particular. The related graphics are intended to aid the data user in acquiring relevant data; it is not appropriate to use the related graphics as data. The National Park Service gives no warranty, expressed or implied, as to the accuracy, reliability, or completeness of these data. It is strongly recommended that these data are directly acquired from an NPS server and not indirectly through other sources which may have changed the data in some way. Although these data have been processed successfully on a computer system at the National Park Service, no warranty expressed or implied is made regarding the utility of the data on another system or for general or scientific purposes, nor shall the act of distribution constitute any such warranty. This disclaimer applies both to individual use of the data and aggregate use with other data.</distliab><stdorder><digform><digtinfo><formname>ESRI Shapefile </formname></digtinfo><digtopt><onlinopt><computer><networka><networkr>http://nrdata.nps.gov/programs/Lands/moja_tracts.zip </networkr></networka></computer></onlinopt></digtopt></digform><fees>None </fees></stdorder><resdesc>moja.shp and moja_boundary.shp </resdesc><custom>
To get a hard copy plot, contact Land Resources Program
Center for replacement costs and turnaround times.
</custom></distinfo><metainfo><metd Sync="FALSE">20220915  </metd><metc><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>Pacific West Region Land Resources Program Center -San Francisco </cntorg><cntper>Regional Cartographer </cntper></cntorgp><cntpos>Cartographic Technician </cntpos><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and physical address</addrtype><address>333 Bush Street, Suite 500 </address><city>San Francisco </city><state>CA </state><postal>94104-2828 </postal><country>USA</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>415-623-2123 </cntvoice><cntfax>415-623-2381 </cntfax><cntemail>PPFL_LandsNet@nps.gov </cntemail><hours>0730-1700 MST M-F </hours></cntinfo></metc><metstdn Sync="FALSE">FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata </metstdn><metstdv Sync="FALSE">FGDC-STD-001-1998 </metstdv><metextns><onlink Sync="FALSE">http://www.esri.com/metadata/esriprof80.html</onlink><metprof Sync="FALSE">ESRI Metadata Profile</metprof></metextns><metextns><onlink Sync="FALSE">http://nrdata.nps.gov/profiles/NPS_Profile.xml</onlink><metprof Sync="FALSE">NPS Metadata Profile</metprof></metextns><langmeta Sync="FALSE">en</langmeta><mettc Sync="FALSE">local time</mettc></metainfo><mdLang><languageCode value="eng"></languageCode></mdLang><mdChar><CharSetCd value="004"></CharSetCd></mdChar><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005"></ScopeCd></mdHrLv><mdDateSt Sync="TRUE">20220915</mdDateSt><mdStanName>ArcGIS Metadata</mdStanName><mdStanVer>1.0</mdStanVer><distInfo><distributor><distorCont><rpIndName>Roger Johnson </rpIndName><rpOrgName>NPS - Land Resources Division, WASO-FC </rpOrgName><rpPosName>Chief Cartographer </rpPosName><rpCntInfo><cntPhone><voiceNum>970-484-6428 </voiceNum><faxNum>970-484-6432 </faxNum></cntPhone><cntAddress addressType="both"><delPoint>301 South Howes Street Suite 208 </delPoint><city>Fort Collins </city><adminArea>CO </adminArea><postCode>80522 </postCode><country>US</country><eMailAdd>roger_m_johnson@nps.gov </eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntHours>7:00am-5:30pm Mountain Monday-Thursday </cntHours></rpCntInfo><role><RoleCd value="005"></RoleCd></role></distorCont><distorOrdPrc><resFees>None </resFees></distorOrdPrc><distorFormat><formatName>ESRI Shapefile </formatName></distorFormat><distorTran><onLineSrc><linkage>http://nrdata.nps.gov/programs/Lands/moja_tracts.zip </linkage></onLineSrc></distorTran></distributor><distributor><distorCont><rpIndName>Roger Johnson </rpIndName><rpOrgName>NPS - Land Resources Division, WASO-FC </rpOrgName><rpPosName>Chief Cartographer </rpPosName><rpCntInfo><cntPhone><voiceNum>970-484-6428 </voiceNum><faxNum>970-484-6432 </faxNum></cntPhone><cntAddress addressType="both"><delPoint>301 South Howes Street Suite 208 </delPoint><city>Fort Collins </city><adminArea>CO </adminArea><postCode>80522 </postCode><country>US</country><eMailAdd>roger_m_johnson@nps.gov </eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntHours>7:00am-5:30pm Mountain Monday-Thursday </cntHours></rpCntInfo><role><RoleCd value="005"></RoleCd></role></distorCont><distorOrdPrc><ordInstr>
To get a hard copy plot, contact Land Resources Program
Center for replacement costs and turnaround times.
</ordInstr></distorOrdPrc></distributor><distTranOps><onLineSrc><linkage>http://nrdata.nps.gov/programs/Lands/moja_tracts.zip </linkage></onLineSrc></distTranOps></distInfo><dataIdInfo><idCitation><resTitle>Mojave National Preserve Tract and Boundary Data </resTitle><date><pubDate>2020-09-15</pubDate></date><resEd>20200915 </resEd><citRespParty><rpOrgName>Department of the Interior (DOI), National Park Service (NPS), Land Resources Division (LRD), Pacific West Land Resources Program Center </rpOrgName><role><RoleCd value="006"></RoleCd></role></citRespParty><citRespParty><rpOrgName>National Park Service Land Resources Division </rpOrgName><rpCntInfo><cntAddress><delPoint>San Francisco, CA </delPoint></cntAddress></rpCntInfo><role><RoleCd value="010"></RoleCd></role></citRespParty><presForm><PresFormCd value="005"></PresFormCd></presForm><presForm><fgdcGeoform>vector digital data</fgdcGeoform></presForm><citRespParty><rpIndName>Maria Anulacion</rpIndName><rpOrgName>Pacific West Region Land Resources Program Center -San Francisco </rpOrgName><rpPosName>Cartographer</rpPosName><role><RoleCd value="007"></RoleCd></role><rpCntInfo><cntAddress addressType="both"><delPoint>168 S. Jackson St.</delPoint><city>Seattle</city><adminArea>WA</adminArea><postCode>98104</postCode><eMailAdd>maria_anulacion@nps.gov</eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntPhone><voiceNum tddtty="">(206) 220-4094</voiceNum></cntPhone></rpCntInfo></citRespParty></idCitation><idAbs>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;These ESRI shape files are of National Park Service tract and boundary data that was created by the Land Resources Division. Tracts are numbered and created by the regional cartographic staff at the Land Resources Program Centers and are associated to the Land Status Maps. This data should be used to display properties that NPS owns and properties that NPS may have some type of interest such as scenic easements or right of ways.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</idAbs><idPurp>This data is intended to keep a record of ownership information. Tracts can represent several types of interest like fee and scenic easement, and can be under several types of ownership like NPS owned, private, other federal, state or county. This data set provides accurate and reliable ownership data for park management and acquisition priorities.</idPurp><idStatus><ProgCd value="001"></ProgCd></idStatus><idPoC><rpIndName>Roger M. Johnson </rpIndName><rpOrgName>NPS - Land Resources Division, WASO -Fort Collins, CO </rpOrgName><rpPosName>Cartographer </rpPosName><rpCntInfo><cntPhone><voiceNum tddtty="">970-484-6428 </voiceNum><faxNum>970-484-6432 </faxNum></cntPhone><cntAddress addressType="both"><delPoint>301 South Howes Street, Suite 208 </delPoint><city>Fort Collins </city><adminArea>CO </adminArea><postCode>80521 </postCode><country>USA </country><eMailAdd>roger_m_johnson@nps.gov </eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntHours>0700-17:30 MST M-F </cntHours></rpCntInfo><role><RoleCd value="007"></RoleCd></role></idPoC><resMaint><maintFreq><MaintFreqCd value="continually "></MaintFreqCd></maintFreq></resMaint><placeKeys><keyword>United States</keyword><keyword>National Park Service</keyword><keyword>Mojave National Preserve</keyword><keyword>Pacific West</keyword><keyword>California</keyword></placeKeys><placeKeys><thesaName><resTitle>National Park System Unit Name Thesaurus</resTitle></thesaName></placeKeys><placeKeys><thesaName><resTitle>National Park System Unit Code Thesaurus</resTitle></thesaName></placeKeys><themeKeys><thesaName><resTitle>ISO 19115 Topic Category</resTitle></thesaName><keyword>Boundaries</keyword><keyword>Planning Cadastre</keyword></themeKeys><themeKeys><keyword>Boundary</keyword><keyword>Ownership</keyword><keyword>Parcels</keyword><keyword>Tracts</keyword><keyword>LRDCAB</keyword></themeKeys><themeKeys><thesaName><resTitle>National Park Service Theme Category Thesaurus</resTitle></thesaName></themeKeys><searchKeys><keyword>Boundaries</keyword><keyword>Planning Cadastre</keyword><keyword>Boundary</keyword><keyword>Ownership</keyword><keyword>Parcels</keyword><keyword>Tracts</keyword><keyword>LRDCAB</keyword><keyword>United States</keyword><keyword>National Park Service</keyword><keyword>Mojave National Preserve</keyword><keyword>Pacific West</keyword><keyword>California</keyword></searchKeys><resConst><Consts><useLimit>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;NPS Director's Order #25 states: "Land status maps will be prepared to identify the ownership of the lands within the authorized boundaries of the park unit. These maps, showing ownership and acreage, are the 'official record' of the acreage of Federal and non-federal lands within the park boundaries. While these maps are the official record of the lands and acreage within the unit's authorized boundaries, they are not of survey quality and not intended to be used for survey purposes." As such this data is intended for use as a tool for GIS analysis. It is in no way intended for engineering or legal purposes. The data accuracy is checked against best available sources which may be dated and vary by location. NPS assumes no liability for use of this data. The boundary polygons LRD creates represent the current legislated boundary of a given NPS unit. NPS does not necessarily have full fee ownership or hold another interest (easement, right of way, etc...) in all parcels contained within this boundary. Equivalently NPS may own or have an interest in parcels outside the legislated boundary of a given unit. In order to obtain complete information about current NPS interests both inside and outside the units legislated boundary, the tracts file created by LRD should be used in conjunction with this boundary file created by LRD.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</useLimit></Consts></resConst><resConst><LegConsts><useLimit>Property ownership data is compiled from deeds, plats, surveys, and other source data. These are not engineering quality drawings and should be used for administrative purposes only. The National Park Service shall not be held liable for improper or incorrect use of the data described and/or contained herein. These data and related graphics are not legal documents and are not intended to be used as such. The information contained in these data is dynamic and may change over time. The data are not better than the original sources from which they were derived. It is the responsibility of the data user to use the data appropriately and consistent within the limitations of geospatial data in general and these data in particular. The related graphics are intended to aid the data user in acquiring relevant data; it is not appropriate to use the related graphics as data. The National Park Service gives no warranty, expressed or implied, as to the accuracy, reliability, or completeness of these data. It is strongly recommended that these data are directly acquired from an NPS server and not indirectly through other sources which may have changed the data in some way. Although these data have been processed successfully on a computer system at the National Park Service, no warranty expressed or implied is made regarding the utility of the data on another system or for general or scientific purposes, nor shall the act of distribution constitute any such warranty. This disclaimer applies both to individual use of the data and aggregate use with other data.</useLimit><accessConsts><RestrictCd value="008"></RestrictCd></accessConsts><othConsts>None </othConsts></LegConsts></resConst><dataLang><languageCode value="eng"></languageCode></dataLang><dataExt><geoEle><GeoBndBox><exTypeCode>true</exTypeCode><westBL>-116.164549</westBL><eastBL>-114.949471 </eastBL><northBL>35.591233 </northBL><southBL>34.716968 </southBL></GeoBndBox></geoEle></dataExt><dataExt><exDesc>Beginning date is the first recorded conveyance date. Ending date is set to the last day the data set was updated. </exDesc><tempEle><TempExtent><exTemp><TM_Period><tmBegin>1994-10-31</tmBegin><tmEnd>2020-09-15</tmEnd></TM_Period></exTemp></TempExtent></tempEle></dataExt><dataChar><CharSetCd value="004"></CharSetCd></dataChar><tpCat><TopicCatCd value="003"></TopicCatCd></tpCat></dataIdInfo><dqInfo><dqScope><scpLvl><ScopeCd value="005"></ScopeCd></scpLvl></dqScope><report type="DQConcConsis" dimension=""><measDesc>Link and node polygon topology is created using Autodesk Civil3D 2015 project.. The data is then exported to ESRI shape file format and reprojected from it's native Autodesk coordinate system to NAD83 generic latitude and longitude, LL83. </measDesc></report><report type="DQCompOm" dimension=""><measDesc>Information contained in LRD's land ownership databases is updated nightly however tract polygons are posted to the NPS Data Store on a monthly basis. Users can ensure parcel polygons have up to date ownership attribution after the publication date by contacting your regional LRD office or downloading the Current_Tract_Ownership_Data file located on the NPS Data Store (http://science.nature.nps.gov/nrdata/) in a dBase format. Please contact the data originator with any suggested corrections and updates. LRD's boundary polygons represent the current legislated boundary of a given NPS unit. NPS does not necessarily have full fee ownership or hold another interest (easement, right of way, etc...) in all parcels contained within this boundary. Equivalently NPS may own or have an interest in parcels outside the legislated boundary of a given unit. In order to obtain complete information about current NPS interests both inside and outside the units legislated boundary, LRD's tracts files should also be downloaded and used in conjunction with LRD's boundary files. </measDesc></report><dataLineage><prcStep><stepDesc>Minor revisions was done on 9/15/2020. No revision was made to the boundary. Tract 160-03 was divided into three tracts. The geometry Tracts 144-49 and 144-50 was adjusted (See C.O. # 114). The topology was updated on 9/18/2019, tract 144-14 was divided into three tracts and Tract 192-22 was divided into two tracts. PUBLIC LAW No. 116-90 (03/12/2019) Natural Resources Management Act boundary of preserve was adjusted to include 25.00 acres of of Bureau of Land Management land located in Baker, California. So the tract topology also was updated to included the new tract. Tract 114-35 made up three county parcels 0544-291-114 (10.00 ac.), 0544-291-16 (5.00 ac.) and portion of 0544-351-06 (5.00 ac.) All parcels are described as an aliquot parts in Sections 19 and 30 of T 14 N, R 9 E, San Bernardino Base &amp; Meridian. a Only the tract topology was updated due to the acquisitions of 96 tracts done in February of 2017. A minor discrepancy of an aliquot parts description was found by a BLM geographer, therefore boundary of preserve was modified. The discrepancy was located on the E-W south-south 1/64 centerline of Section 10, T 14 N, R 17 E, San Bernardine Base &amp; Meridian. The boundary was moved 660 feet easterly on said centerline from C-S-SE 1/64 corner of said section to SE-SE-1/64 corner of Section 10 to be consisted with legal description of the preserve. The layer of Tract 109-03 was revised from Tract to Tract-Sec. There were four individual tracts each tract was divided into two tracts. The boundary between Tracts 197-14 and 197-15 was revised. Boundary adjustment published in the Federal Register on June 14, 2013 [NPS-PWR-MOJA-12321; PS.SMOJA0003]. SUMMARY: Notice the boundary of Mojave National Preserve is modified to include 7.12 acres of improved land identified as Tract 103-28 and to exclude 48.14 acres of improved land identified as Tract 114-05. The entire line work of park boundary and the individual tracts were re-drawn based on the latest BLM CadNSDI PLSS Data a geodatebase for State of California (FGDB dated 09/19/2011). In process of re-mapping of the digitized centerlines of the Kingston Road and Nipton Road was done in ArcGIS. Cogo-ing hardcopies of right-of-way maps of Interstate 15 and Interstate 40. These right-of-way maps were provided by the Department of Transportation of the State of California (CALTRANS District 8). Park boundary of the park in NW portion is right-of-way of Interstate 15 and in southern portion is the right-of-way of Interstate 40. ROW linework in section 1 of T 15N R 11E, sections 5 and 6 T 15N R 12E, and sections 24, 25, 26, 27, 31, 32, and 33 of T 16N R 12E were rotated around the section corner common to sections 17, 18, 19, and 20 of T 16N R 12E 1 degree. ROW linework in section 22 T 15N R 14E, and sections 32, 33, and 34 T 16N R 14 E was rotated around the west quarter corner of section 22 T 15N R 14E 0d 40'. ROW linework in sections 1, 2, 11, 14, 15, 21, and 22 T 13N R 8E was rotated around the section corner common to sections 25, 26, 35, and 36 of T 14N R 8E 0d40'. ROW linework in section 36 T 14N R 8E and sections 20, 29, 30, and 31 T 14N R 9E were rotated around the section corner common to sections 16, 17, 20, and 21 T 14N R 9E 0d25'. ROW linework in sections 1, 10, 11, 15, 16, and 21 T 14N R 9E, section 6 T 14N R 10E, and sections 31 and 32 T 15N R 10E were rotated around the corner common to sections 16, 17, 20, and 21 T 14N R 9E 1d. ROW linework in sections 28 and 29 T 15N R 10E were rotated around the corner common to sections 28, 29, 32, and 33 T 15N R 10E 1d. ROW linework in sections 13, 22, 23, and 24 T 15N R 10E, and sections 8, 9, 10, 11, 17, and 18 in T15N R 11E were rotated around the corner common to sections 21, 22, 27, 28 T 15N R 10E 1d. Tracts 153-04, 153-05, 153-06, 153-07, 153-08, 153-09, 153-10, 153-11, 153-14, 153-15, 153-16, 153-17, 153-18 and portion of 143-03 were transformed X = 7267289.24, Y = 2199939.78 (NE corner of Sec.25) and 7261917.55, Y = 2194560.90 (SW corner of Sec. 25) to account for the ground to grid translation. All of these tracts located in Sec. 25, T. 11 N, R12 E., S.B. B. &amp; M. Two transformed points were derivated from GCDB Data. Tract 118-01A rotated around 1°23’46.54674” from Latitude 35°18” 55.765” N and Longitude 115°33’01.681”W (NAD 83). Tract 103-28 is outside the park boundary and it’s described in the California State Plane Coordinate System of 1983, Zone 5 same as cad file for Mojave NP. NAD83 California State Planes, Zone 5, US Foot was used as the source coordinate system for the Autodesk Civil3D 2012 project. The Autodesk line work is imported, edited, attributed, approved, and a link and node topology is developed both for the tract and boundary data layers according to the procedures described in the Land Acquisition Procedures Manual Chapter 5. The entire unit is created in a geographically contiguous model space and separate layouts representing each individual segment map are created. The tract and boundary data is then reprojected to North American Datum 1983 generic latitude &amp; longitude and exported from Autodesk to an ArcView shape file format in a single step. This data dates back to 2004. It was first made available in 2016.</stepDesc><stepDesc>Update 03212019: Tract and boundary topologies were updated to include 25.00 acres added to preserve per change order #112 Tract 114-35. The tract topology was updated to reflect the changes in change order 8386-11. It was discovered that the parcels had not been assigned separate NPS tract numbers, and that their acreage was mistakenly lumped in with tract 104-01. </stepDesc><stepProc><rpIndName>Ernesto O. Sanchez </rpIndName><rpOrgName>Pacific West Region Land Resources Program Center </rpOrgName><rpPosName>Cartographic Technician </rpPosName><rpCntInfo><cntPhone><voiceNum tddtty="">415-623-2123 </voiceNum><faxNum>415-623-2381 </faxNum></cntPhone><cntAddress addressType="both"><delPoint>333 Bush Street, Suite 500 </delPoint><city>San Francisco </city><adminArea>CA </adminArea><postCode>94104-2828 </postCode><country>US</country><eMailAdd>Ernesto_O_Sanchez@nps.gov </eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntHours>0800- 1700, M-F PST </cntHours></rpCntInfo><role><RoleCd value="009"></RoleCd></role></stepProc><stepSrc type="used"><srcCitatn><resAltTitle>Deeds, Segment Maps, Legal Descriptions and Misc. Maps from the NPS LandsNet Archive (http://landsnet.nps.gov/tractsnet/documents/MOJA/) </resAltTitle></srcCitatn></stepSrc><stepDateTm>2020-09-15T00:00:00</stepDateTm></prcStep><dataSource type=""><srcDesc>tract and boundary geometry, Tract_id, Alpha </srcDesc><srcMedName><MedNameCd value="paper "></MedNameCd></srcMedName><srcScale><rfDenom>1 </rfDenom></srcScale><srcCitatn><resTitle>Legal Descriptions </resTitle><resAltTitle>Legal Descriptions </resAltTitle><date><pubDate>2020-09-15</pubDate></date><resEd>N/A </resEd><citRespParty><rpOrgName>National Park Service - Land Resources Division </rpOrgName><role><RoleCd value="006"></RoleCd></role></citRespParty><citRespParty><rpOrgName>Land Resources Division </rpOrgName><rpCntInfo><cntAddress><delPoint>Pacific West Land Resources Program Center </delPoint></cntAddress></rpCntInfo><role><RoleCd value="010"></RoleCd></role></citRespParty><presForm><PresFormCd value="document - legal description "></PresFormCd></presForm><presForm><fgdcGeoform>document - legal description </fgdcGeoform></presForm><otherCitDet>NA </otherCitDet></srcCitatn><srcExt><exDesc>Beginning Date represents first conveyed date. Ending date is when the data was last updated. </exDesc><tempEle><TempExtent><exTemp><TM_Period><tmBegin>1994-10-31</tmBegin><tmEnd>2020-09-15</tmEnd></TM_Period></exTemp></TempExtent></tempEle></srcExt></dataSource><dataSource type=""><srcDesc>tract and boundary geometry, Tract_id, Alpha </srcDesc><srcMedName><MedNameCd value="paper "></MedNameCd></srcMedName><srcScale><rfDenom>1 </rfDenom></srcScale><srcCitatn><resTitle>Deeds </resTitle><resAltTitle>deeds </resAltTitle><date><pubDate>2020-09-15</pubDate></date><resEd>N/A </resEd><citRespParty><rpOrgName>National Park Service - Land Resources Division </rpOrgName><role><RoleCd value="006"></RoleCd></role></citRespParty><citRespParty><rpOrgName>Land Resources Division </rpOrgName><rpCntInfo><cntAddress><delPoint>Pacific West Land Resources Program Center </delPoint></cntAddress></rpCntInfo><role><RoleCd value="010"></RoleCd></role></citRespParty><presForm><PresFormCd value="document - deed "></PresFormCd></presForm><presForm><fgdcGeoform>document - deed </fgdcGeoform></presForm><otherCitDet>NA </otherCitDet></srcCitatn><srcExt><exDesc>Beginning Date represents first conveyed date. Ending date is when the data was last updated. </exDesc><tempEle><TempExtent><exTemp><TM_Period><tmBegin>1994-10-31</tmBegin><tmEnd>2020-09-15</tmEnd></TM_Period></exTemp></TempExtent></tempEle></srcExt></dataSource><dataSource type=""><srcDesc>tract and boundary geometry, Tract_id, Alpha </srcDesc><srcMedName><MedNameCd value="digital "></MedNameCd></srcMedName><srcScale><rfDenom>1200 - 36000 </rfDenom></srcScale><srcCitatn><resTitle>Segment Maps </resTitle><resAltTitle>segment maps </resAltTitle><date><pubDate>2020-09-15</pubDate></date><resEd>N/A </resEd><citRespParty><rpOrgName>National Park Service - Land Resources Division </rpOrgName><role><RoleCd value="006"></RoleCd></role></citRespParty><citRespParty><rpOrgName>Land Resources Division </rpOrgName><rpCntInfo><cntAddress><delPoint>Pacific West Land Resources Program Center </delPoint></cntAddress></rpCntInfo><role><RoleCd value="010"></RoleCd></role></citRespParty><presForm><PresFormCd value="map - segment map "></PresFormCd></presForm><presForm><fgdcGeoform>map - segment map </fgdcGeoform></presForm><otherCitDet>NA </otherCitDet></srcCitatn><srcExt><exDesc>Beginning Date represents first conveyed date. Ending date is when the data was last updated. </exDesc><tempEle><TempExtent><exTemp><TM_Period><tmBegin>1994-10-31</tmBegin><tmEnd>2020-09-15</tmEnd></TM_Period></exTemp></TempExtent></tempEle></srcExt></dataSource><prcStep><stepDesc>Update 12/9/2021
The value for the Estate attribute of the following tracts was changed to FEE upon acquisition in 2021: Tracts 126-18, 126-22, 126-62, 126-72, 126-74, 126-79, 127-39, 127-48, 144-14, 144-49, 145-09, 145-41, 145-58, 146-41, 146-44, 148-19, 191-14, 191-19, 191-37, 191-41, 192-16, 192-17, 192-22, 192-57, 192-62, 192-65, 195-21, 195-25, 195-30, 196-44, 196-52, 197-13, 197-23, 197-29, 197-35, 198-19, 198-26, 198-35. These tracts are inside the Preserve boundary. No revisions were made to the boundary.</stepDesc><stepProc><rpIndName>Maria Anulacion</rpIndName><rpOrgName>Pacific West Region Land Resources Program Center -San Francisco </rpOrgName><rpPosName>Cartographer</rpPosName><role><RoleCd value="007"></RoleCd></role><rpCntInfo><cntAddress addressType="both"><delPoint>168 S. Jackson St.</delPoint><city>Seattle</city><adminArea>WA</adminArea><postCode>98104</postCode><eMailAdd>maria_anulacion@nps.gov</eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntPhone><voiceNum tddtty="">(206) 220-4094</voiceNum></cntPhone></rpCntInfo><displayName>Maria Anulacion</displayName></stepProc><stepDateTm>2021-12-09T00:00:00</stepDateTm></prcStep><prcStep><stepDesc>Update 3/2/2022. Tract 134-07 was split into 3 tracts: 134-07, 134-15, 134-16. Tract 134-09 was split into 2 tracts: 134-09 and 134-17.</stepDesc><stepDateTm>2022-03-20T00:00:00</stepDateTm></prcStep><prcStep><stepDesc>Update 9/15/2022. Tract 165-08 was added and tract geometry is based on BLM PLSS National Geospatial Data Asset published July 13, 2022. </stepDesc><stepDateTm>2022-09-15T00:00:00</stepDateTm><stepProc><rpIndName>Maria Anulacion</rpIndName><rpOrgName>Pacific West Region Land Resources Program Center -San Francisco </rpOrgName><rpPosName>Cartographer</rpPosName><role><RoleCd value="007"></RoleCd></role><rpCntInfo><cntAddress addressType="both"><delPoint>168 S. Jackson St.</delPoint><city>Seattle</city><adminArea>WA</adminArea><postCode>98104</postCode><eMailAdd>maria_anulacion@nps.gov</eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntPhone><voiceNum tddtty="">(206) 220-4094</voiceNum></cntPhone></rpCntInfo><displayName>Maria Anulacion</displayName></stepProc></prcStep></dataLineage></dqInfo><mdExtInfo><extOnRes><linkage>http://nrdata.nps.gov/profiles/NPS_Profile.xml</linkage><orName>NPS Metadata Profile</orName></extOnRes></mdExtInfo><Esri><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><scaleRange><minScale>1 </minScale><maxScale>1200 - 36000 </maxScale></scaleRange><DataProperties><itemProps><imsContentType export="False"></imsContentType></itemProps></DataProperties><ArcGISProfile>FGDC</ArcGISProfile></Esri><mdContact><rpIndName>Maria Anulacion</rpIndName><rpOrgName>Pacific West Region Land Resources Program Center -San Francisco </rpOrgName><rpPosName>Cartographer</rpPosName><role><RoleCd value="007"></RoleCd></role><rpCntInfo><cntAddress addressType="both"><delPoint>168 S. Jackson St.</delPoint><city>Seattle</city><adminArea>WA</adminArea><postCode>98104</postCode><eMailAdd>maria_anulacion@nps.gov</eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntPhone><voiceNum tddtty="">(206) 220-4094</voiceNum></cntPhone></rpCntInfo><displayName>Maria Anulacion</displayName></mdContact></metadata>
